

# GREG







## **MARTIROSIAN**

Angular Front-end developer

#### **ABOUT ME**

Passionate about web technologies, particularly frontend and Angular. Constantly seek out and study information on native JavaScript and frameworks. Having frequently worked with backend technologies, approach tasks comprehensively, proposing solutions for discussion with colleagues.

Also being a mentor at rsschool, I help students understand angular and write clean code

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Russian
- Spanish
- Armenian

#### **SKILLS**

- Angular | RxJs | NgRx
- JavaScript | TypeScript
- HTML | CSS | SCSS
- React | Redux
- Gulp | Webpack
- Node.JS | Nest.JS
- Figma
- Unit testing
- Scully | Srapi
- jQuery | Bootstrap

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Angular Front-End developer, 2022 - 2024 GCORE

Worked with Angular versions 15, 16 on the company website. One of my key projects was developing a cloud products calculator, which involved complex logic and multiple user interactions. Utilized a range of technologies, including Angular, RxJS, Strapi, Scully, and Nest.js with TypeORM and PostgreSQL, to generate data from JSON prices for the frontend and integrate it into the calculator.

#### Front-End developer, 2020 - 2022 Freelancer

Worked with several clients at various stages of development, creating a range of websites including blogs, online shops, and landing pages. Also designed elements for the sites to ensure they were visually appealing and functional. Utilized JavaScript, SCSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, OpenCart, and jQuery.

#### **EDUCATION**

Front-End developer / JavaScript, 2021 - 2022

The Rolling Scopes School

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), 2023

MGSI - External DPO - GDPR

**JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures 2021** freeCodeCamp



+34 641 294 406



greg.martinez.dev@gmail.com